{
   "questions":[
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-a1",
        "questionType":"audio",
        "question":"Good morning, Good afternoon, Good night",
        "answers": [
         "Good morning",
         "Good afternoon",
         "Good night"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":"Good afternoon"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a2",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Good morning, Good afternoon, Goodbye",
        "answers": [
          "Good morning",
          "Good afternoon",
          "Goodbye"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Good morning"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a3",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Principal, Friend, Teacher",
        "answers": [
          "Principal",
          "Friend",
          "Teacher"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Teacher"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a4",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Greek, Greet, Greed",
        "answers": [
          "Greek",
          "Greet",
          "Greed"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Greet"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a5",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Moniter, Monitor, Moniker",
        "answers": [
          "Moniter",
          "Monitor",
          "Moniker"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Monitor"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a6",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Schoolmate, Classroom, Classmate",
        "answers": [
          "Schoolmate",
          "Classroom",
          "Classmate"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Classmate"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a7",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Gardener, Gadener, Gardenor",
        "answers": [
          "Gardener",
          "Gadener",
          "Gardenor"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Gardener"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a8",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Hello, Hallo, Hullo",
        "answers": [
          "Hello",
          "Hallo",
          "Hullo"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hello"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a9",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Freind, Fried, Friend",
        "answers": [
          "Freind",
          "Fried",
          "Friend"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Friend"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a10",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Good morning, Good afternoon, Goodbye",
        "answers": [
          "Good morning",
          "Good afternoon",
          "Goodbye"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Goodbye"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a11",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Janitor, Lender, Leader",
        "answers": [
          "Janitor",
          "Lender",
          "Leader"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Leader"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a12",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Princes, Principle, Princess",
        "answers": [
          "Princes",
          "Principle",
          "Princess"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Principle"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a13",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Monitor, Driver, Janitor",
        "answers": [
          "Monitor",
          "Driver",
          "Janitor"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Driver"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a14",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Cockroach, Coach, Couch",
        "answers": [
          "Cockroach",
          "Coach",
          "Couch"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Coach"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a15",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Library, Libraries, Librarian",
        "answers": [
          "Library",
          "Libraries",
          "Librarian"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Librarian"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a16",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "English, Chinese, Maths",
        "answers": [
          "English",
          "Chinese",
          "Maths"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "English"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a17",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "English, Chinese, Maths",
        "answers": [
          "English",
          "Chinese",
          "Maths"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Chinese"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a18",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Leader, Driver, Janitor",
        "answers": [
          "Leader",
          "Driver",
          "Janitor"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Janitor"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a19",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Students, Student, Study",
        "answers": [
          "Students",
          "Student",
          "Study"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Student"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u1-a20",
        "questionType": "audio",
        "question": "Prefect, Perfect, Principal",
        "answers": [
          "Prefect",
          "Perfect",
          "Principal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Prefect"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e1",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have many colors. I make your picture more beautiful.",
        "answers": [
          "Crayons",
          "Erasers",
          "Pencils"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Crayons"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e2",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I am very important. I help all students carry all the things to school.",
        "answers": [
          "Folder",
          "Lunchbox",
          "School Bag"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "School Bag"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e3",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I make sure your book is clean and neat. I help correct your mistakes.",
        "answers": [
          "Eraser",
          "Ruler",
          "Pen"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Eraser"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e4",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "You need me when you are hungry at recess.",
        "answers": [
          "Bottle",
          "Snacks",
          "Lunchbox"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Snacks"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e5",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have two legs and I am sharp. I can cut paper but also your finger.",
        "answers": [
          "Sharpener",
          "Scissors",
          "Glue"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Scissors"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e6",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I can speak English, Chinese and even numbers too. You can learn a lot from me.",
        "answers": [
          "Highlighters",
          "Folders",
          "Books"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Books"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e7",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "You need me in math class. I help you find out how long the line is.",
        "answers": [
          "Eraser",
          "Pen",
          "Ruler"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ruler"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e8",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I help you remember what your teacher said.",
        "answers": [
          "Exercise",
          "Notebook",
          "Stapler"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Notebook"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e9",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "If you forget to bring me, you will be very thirsty all day.",
        "answers": [
          "Bottle",
          "Lunchbox",
          "Snacks"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bottle"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u3-e10",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I usually wear blue, red or black. Your teacher likes red the most.",
        "answers": [
          "Pens",
          "Pencils",
          "Crayons"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Pens"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e1",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have black and white fur, and I love to eat bamboo.",
        "answers": [
          "Zebra",
          "Tiger",
          "Panda"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Panda"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e2",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have a long nose that can pick up things.",
        "answers": [
          "Elephant",
          "Giraffe",
          "Rabbit"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Elephant"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e3",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "My ears are so long, they almost touch the ground.",
        "answers": [
          "Rabbit",
          "Monkey",
          "Giraffe"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Rabbit"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e4",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have a long neck. I can touch the leaves.",
        "answers": [
          "Elephant",
          "Giraffe",
          "Monkey"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Giraffe"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e5",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I'm the king of the jungle. I have loud roar.",
        "answers": [
          "Hippo",
          "Snake",
          "Lion"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Lion"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e6",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have a round tummy and a short tail. My thick brown fur keeps me warm.",
        "answers": [
          "Panda",
          "Bear",
          "Hippo"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bear"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e7",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I am long. I have no legs and I slide.",
        "answers": [
          "Giraffe",
          "Tiger",
          "Snake"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Snake"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e8",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have black and white strips. I run on the grass.",
        "answers": [
          "Zebra",
          "Tiger",
          "Panda"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zebra"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e9",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I have a long tail and I swing from tree to tree.",
        "answers": [
          "Rabbit",
          "Monkey",
          "Giraffe"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Monkey"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p1u5-e10",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I am gray in color. I live near the river.",
        "answers": [
          "Tiger",
          "Crocodile",
          "Hippo"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hippo"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e1",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I want to mail a letter.",
        "answers": [
          "Post office",
          "School",
          "Police station"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Post office"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e2",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "My hair is too long. I want to have a haircut.",
        "answers": [
        "Restaurant",
        "Salon",
        "Cafe"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Salon"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e3",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "My mom says I can play with Sally after my piano class.",
        "answers": [
        "Park",
        "Clinic",
        "Temple"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Park"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e4",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "Oh no! I think I lost my wallet.",
        "answers": [
        "Fire station",
        "Police station",
        "Post office"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Police station"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e5",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I fell from a window and broke my arm!",
        "answers": [
        "Fire station",
        "Police station",
        "Hospital"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hospital"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e6",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I feel tired and hungry. Can we have a break?",
        "answers": [
        "Bank",
        "Museum",
        "Cafe"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cafe"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e7",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "My family believes in god. We go to pray every Sunday.",
        "answers": [
        "Church",
        "Hospital",
        "Home"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Church"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e8",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "Uncle Billy is going to get some money.",
        "answers": [
        "Supermarket",
        "Mall",
        "Bank"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bank"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e9",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I am excited to see Miss Wong and my classmates again!",
        "answers": [
        "Home",
        "Park",
        "School"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "School"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u1-e10",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "It's 6 pm. I need to go or my mom will be angry!",
        "answers": [
        "Home",
        "Cafe",
        "School"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Home"
      },
      {
        "qid": "p2u6-e1",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I keep animals healthy and happy.",
        "answers": [
        "vet",
        "nurse",
        "chef"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "vet"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e2",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I teach children new knowledge.",
        "answers": [
        "artist",
        "teacher",
        "singer"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "teacher"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e3",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I help take care of the sick people.",
        "answers": [
        "waiter",
        "thieves",
        "nurse"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "nurse"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e4",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I can write songs and perform in front of people.",
        "answers": [
        "singer",
        "policeman",
        "housewife"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "singer"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e5",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I take good care of my children and spend time with them.",
        "answers": [
        "doctor",
        "housewife",
        "nurse"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "housewife"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e6",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I catch bad people and protect the city.",
        "answers": [
        "postman",
        "pilot",
        "policeman"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "policeman"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e7",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I travel around the world very often.",
        "answers": [
        "postman",
        "pilot",
        "policeman"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "pilot"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e8",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I look after the shop and sell my goods to you.",
        "answers": [
        "waitress",
        "artist",
        "shopkeeper"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "shopkeeper"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e9",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I draw beautiful paintings and make good sculptures.",
        "answers": [
        "waitress",
        "artist",
        "shopkeeper"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "artist"
        },
        {
        "qid": "p2u6-e10",
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "I help bring letters to you.",
        "answers": [
        "postman",
        "pilot",
        "policeman"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "postman"
        }
   ]
}
